

Front End Developer

Odessa +38 (063) 34 19 913 vinnik.anna83@gmail.com

SUMMARY

Hello, my name is Anna Vynnyk, I am 22 years old. One and a half years I have been developing websites on freelance. I work with libraries Animate.css, WOW.js and I have basic knowledge of the jQuery library. For development I use the WebStorm environment. I am fond of UI / UX and web design. I use Photoshop and Figma to create layouts.. I have experience with the Wordpress engine.

in /Ann Vynnyk

/SlezaKlouna

/@proxy_cat

EXPERIENCE

Freelance

Web site development | June 2018 - 2019

Interface design development for the customer. Creation of sites on various subjects.

Work examples:

- Online store with a separate landing page for Intersolar solar panels

intersolar.com.ua

- Introductory site for the online club SmelClub smelclub.com.ua
- Landing to familiarize yourself with the Orient line of watches

orient-multi-calendar.shop-x.in.ua

• Thesis project

stat.kitkb.co.ua | February 2019 - November 2019

Development of an analytical system for building ratings of disciplines, programming languages and technologies based on questionnaires

EDUCATION

Faculty of Computer Engineering, Programming and Cyber Defense

ONAFT | 2018 - 2019 | master

Graduated with honors. During my studies, I participated in scientific conferences and published in scientific journals

Green Forest

English courses | November 2018 - July 2019

Hillel

Front-end Pro Coure | November 2019 - now

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Pre-Intermediate English is available at Green Forest courses.







SKILLS

JavaScript

HTML

CSS

Illustrator

Photoshop

Figma